Garrett Fite

garrett.fite@gmail.com | 817-933-1634 | Godley, TX

LinkedIn: https://tinyurl.com/pet5dtc3
Github: https://github.com/Stranded-Helix
Portfolio: https://tinyurl.com/3x9w39b5

Entry level developer with a background in customer service and inventory management. My aim is to create well structured programs and features using my previous experience using a multitude of different applications in the workplace and at home. Known for my drive to learn and problem solving skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend: HTML5, CSS, JQuery, Javascript, XAML, WPF

Backend: C#, MySQL, SQL, MongoDB, NoSQL, Express, Node, ReactJS, Handlebars

PROJECTS

Stolen Canvas | Repo: https://tinyurl.com/4saevnz4 | Deployed: https://tinyurl.com/cpvsh37b

- E-commerce site handling mock sales of great works of art
- Role: Back-End: Database, Routing, APIs, Authorization, Accounts
- Tools/Languages: Javascript, node.js, HTML, CSS, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize

Tech Blog | Repo: https://tinyurl.com/638xrbsa | Deployed: https://tinyurl.com/mbja3ck6

- Blog website with posting, comments, and auto-logoff
- Role: Full-Stack: Database Models, Routing, Front-End
- Tools/Languages: Javascript, node.js, HTML, CSS, Handlebars, MySQL

Global Nibz | Repo: https://tinyurl.com/ruwjxpbv | Deployed: https://tinyurl.com/xzycdtz4

- Randomly selects food items for adventurous or indecisive eaters
- Role: Back-End : API calls and local storage
- Tools/Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS, Edamame API

Barcode Generator | Repo: https://tinyurl.com/39eu95va

- Generates a Code 128 barcode image from user input
- Tools/Languages: C#

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wright Tire Company IT Specialist

Sept 2016 - Jan 2018, Aug 2021 - Current Cleburne, TX

Linebarger Goggan Blair & Sampson, LLP Bankruptcy Specialist

Jan 2018 - Jan 2021 Dallas, TX

Bruckner Truck Sales

Aug 2013 - Sept 2016

Part Sales Associate Lubbock, TX

EDUCATION

Southern Methodist University, Dallas, TX

Full Stack Web Developer Certificate

Jul 2021

Godley High School, Godley, TX
High School Diploma
May 2010

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

George N. Parks Leadership Training Nationwide Aviation Private Pilot Training